<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dory Alexander</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dory Alexander</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 12:18:30 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jamaica</title>
      <link>/posts/jamaica/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 12:18:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/jamaica/</guid>
      <description>One of my favourite things in Mexico is agua de jamaica. It&amp;rsquo;s refreshing, healthy and tastes like fruit punch. I usually order it without sugar, but this one place - Ramiro&amp;rsquo;s Cocina in Merida - makes it with strawberry juice and serves it with a salted rim. Delicious and refreshing on a hot Yucatan afternoon. Yum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Resume Challenge</title>
      <link>/posts/cloud-resume-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 18:22:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/cloud-resume-challenge/</guid>
      <description>I first heard about the cloud resume challenge a few months ago while studying for the AWS SysOps Administrator certification. The premise is using several AWS services to create a resume website that practically demonstrates the skills needed for a cloud engineering job.
The basics of the challenge are:
The site is hosted as a S3 static website CloudFront is used to provide a CDN as well as HTTPS The website uses HTML and CSS in such a way as to create a pleasant design The site has a visitor counter that uses a combination of Javascript and a DynamoDB backend that communicates through an AWS API gateway Source control is used and checks are done for any Python code running Lambda functions to update your database You incorporate some element of IaC for updating your website Finally, you post about what you have learned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo and AWS Amplify</title>
      <link>/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 20:36:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hugo along with jekyll have been the go-to frameworks for static website hosting for a while now. I find github pages to be the most common way to host a hugo site but Amplify only takes a few clicks to configure everything - especially if you&amp;rsquo;re using Route53 for DNS. Personally, I love AWS but dislike Amazon as a company. Luckily Amplify is free tier elegible so you can host away, guilt free!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
